地球百子  前情提要
这是什么
and what is this?
这就是我们制造宿主的方法
this is how we make hosts.
骨髓
bone marrow?
你要让她的心脏停止跳动吗
you're stopping her heart?
死亡使约瑟芬的思维
death causes her mind
回到驱动上
to back up onto the drive.
我取出驱动之后
i take it out.
再重启克拉克的心脏
we get clarke back.
她为什么没有醒来
why isn't she waking up?
克拉克
clarke?
赤日毒素无处不在
the red sun toxin's everywhere.
- 你们把它武器化了  - 西蒙妮把它武器化了
- you weaponized it. - simone did.
作为她调整协议的一部分
it was part of our adjustment protocol.
把它释放到水中
releasing it in the water
在不引发大规模
will trigger an evacuation
精神错乱的情况下启动疏散机制
without inducing a mass psychosis.
我们得在开始之前进去
we'll need to be inside before it starts,
这意味着  我扮成约瑟芬
which means...i go as josephine.
行刑之后  我们找到了更多涂鸦
after the execution, we found more graffiti.
天知道那些逃犯传播了什么病毒
who knows what poison those escaped prisoners are spreading.
他们的中一员已经杀死了西蒙妮
one of them already killed simone.
如果情况继续发展  他们迟早会冲我们来
if this continues, they are going to come for us.
目前  他们的叛乱
right now, their rebellion
正处在一个关键的转折点
is at a tipping point.
今晚必须粉碎他们
must crush it tonight.
让一切回归正常
get everything back to normal.
当我们的人民看到  我们全体回归时
when our people see all of us returned at once,
他们将跪倒在地
they will fall to their knees.
我们应该先杀了你的
we should've killed you first.
在我们重获自由后  你就会被火焰吞噬
once we're free, you will burn.
好吧  这有点夸张了吧
well, that's a little dramatic.
你们都会被烈火吞噬
you will all burn!
你摆脱不了我们的
you will not get rid of us!
我们是永生不死的
we are eternal!
守卫
guards,
把医生们带过来
bring the doctors.
别动
stay still.
她会扯掉静脉注射
she'll tear out the ivs.
我们必须再来一次
we have to take her again.
我知道你们在做什么  雷耶斯
i know what you're doing, reyes.
你自作聪明
you think you're smart enough
想要甩掉我
to get rid of me?
如果你不停下  我就杀了这个孩子
if you don't stop, i will kill this child.
这样好多了  谢谢你
that's better. thank you.
好了
there.
你感觉如何
how do you feel?
绝妙的约瑟芬
peachy keen josephine.
拜托  我不是她
oh, stop it. i'm not her.
我会杀了你
i will kill you for this.
我曾经相信自己永远不会
i once believed that i would never
犯下背德之事
stray from the moral path,
结果我在第一次日食杀死了我的家人
and then i killed my family in the first eclipse.
为了让他们回来  我什么都会做
i'd have done anything to bring them back.
所以我相信你
so i believe you.
你还有多少瓶血清
how many doses of the serum do you have?
4瓶  包括给西蒙妮的那份
4, including the one your people
你的人把它带到了机械车间
took to the machine shop for simone.
今晚6位普莱姆必将重生
6 primes must be resurrected tonight.
还需要两瓶
that's two more doses.
玛蒂活不下来的
madi wouldn't survive that.
如果你做不到
if it's too hard for you to continue,
我的治疗师可以接手
my healers will take your place.
他们已经熟悉流程了
they're already familiar with the process.
不会有问题的
it would be no trouble.
不用  我可以做到
no. i can do it.
很好  记住  这是让你
good. remember, this was the deal
活命的条件
that saved you from the pyre.
但愿不会有变
i'd hate for that to change.
拜拜
toodle-loo.
地 球 百 子
第六季        第12集
翻译： 噬魂师  文睿菌
翻译： ASTEROID
翻译：兔兔秃了
翻译： RossyGeng
校对： 文睿菌
时间轴/特效：小螺号
统筹：Kate
总监：麦斯
我们现在做什么
what do we do now?
我们等着
now we wait.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
克拉克会搞定的
clarke will get it down.
你
you.
你可以进去帮她
you can go in and help her.
怎么帮
how, bell?
因为杰德  他们已经知道他长什么样了
they know what he looks like from jade.
再说了  这和计划不符
besides, it's not the plan.
所有人  注意隐蔽
everyone, stand down. stay low.
不要被巡逻发现
out of sight of the hourly patrols.
我离开了他们
i left them.
所以他们还活着
and that's why they're still alive.
你不能这样说
you don't know that.
你也听到墨菲说的了
you heard murphy.
厄科有麻烦了
echo's in trouble.
厄科很坚强  她会没事的
echo's strong. she'll be ok.
每个人总是这样认为
everybody always thinks that.
我他妈也是
hell, i do it, too.
但事实是  在崩溃之前  人总认为自己没事
the truth is... you're fine until you're not.
墨菲说他会帮忙
and murphy said he'd help.
真让人安心
real comforting.
有点信心
have some faith.
请慢用
enjoy.
得了吧  你知道自己想吃一点的
come on. you know you want some of this.
他们把我们绑在桩子上  约翰
they tied us to stakes, john.
打算把我们活活烧死
they were gonna burn us alive.
你还想和他们要过家家
and you still want to play house with them?
那我们的朋友怎么办
what about our friends?
我们怎么才能救他们
this is how we save them.
想想吧  每个人都只是想要活下去
think about it. everyone's just trying to survive,
哪怕是拉塞尔
even russell.
我们只要让他明白
we just need to make him see
让我们活着
that it's in his best interest
对他最有利
to keep all of us alive.
对我们来说  这意味着永远活着
in our case, forever.
你肯定饿坏了
you must be starving.
先吃点东西
let's get you something to eat.
吃饱喝足后  我需要你准备
after that, i need you to handle
命名日的事情
the naming day preparations.
我不饿  我才刚回来
i'm not hungry and i just got back.
让普丽娅去做
get priya to do it.
她是工程师  不是派对策划师
she's an engineer, not a party planner.
你有去过我的派对吗
have you been to one of my parties?
好吧  我让普丽娅去做
fine. i'll get priya to do it.
很好  现在
good. now,
如果我再打扮成这样
if i spend one more minute like this,
就要找个地缝钻进去了
i will spontaneously combust from the shame.
去把自己收拾一下  我会复活你的母亲
go get cleaned up. i'll resurrect your mother.
等等
wait.
这是不是意味着厄科还活着
does that mean echo's still alive?
她的意思是
what she's saying is
不是所有人都能成为夜之血脉
now that anyone can be a nightblood,
你可以用别人吗
maybe you use someone else?
别发牢骚了
oh, stop your whining.
到底想不想永生了
do you want to be immortal or not?
如果你成为了普莱姆
because if you become primes
这场革命继续开展
and this revolution spreads,
他们也会冲着你们来的
they're coming for you, too.
嘿  妈妈回来的时候  我想见证那个时刻
hey, i want to be there when mom comes back.
等我一下
wait for me?
当然  甜心  动作快点
of course, sweetheart. be quick.
我敬佩你对朋友的忠诚
i admire your loyalty to your friends,
但我得知道你和我们还站在同一战线
but i need to know if you're still with us.
当然
of course we are.
绝对的
absolutely.
你要知道  如果我和我的家人
still, you should know if anything happens
遭遇任何不测  我的守卫将
to me or my family, my guards have orders--
说的够多了 我们加入
enough said. we're in.
很好
good.
让我介绍一下你的新身份
now let me tell you about your new identities.
谢谢
thank you.
她的身体太虚弱了  不能再抽骨髓了
she's too weak for another bone marrow extraction.
你还有多久能移除掉暗黑指挥官
how close are you to removing sheidheda?
我在努力  但是没有笔记的话
i'm trying, but without the notebook,
我  我没有办法绕过人工智能
i--i can't get past that ai.
她说如果你不住手的话
she said if you don't stop,
那个孩子会死
the child will die.
我听到了
i heard her.
所以要么是他杀了她  要么是拉塞尔
so either he kills her, or russell does?
我会担心拉塞尔
i'll worry about russell.
艾比
abby!
从我身上取吧
we'll take the doses from me.
瑞文  继续
raven, keep trying.
杰克森  我们可以做到的
jackson, we can do this.
我没事
i'll be fine.
我们都有麻烦
none of this is fine.
看着我  我知道这很困难
look at me. i know it's hard.
但我们别无选择
we don't have a choice.
每个战争犯都是这样说的
said by every war criminal ever.
我不应该对你说那些话的
i shouldn't have said that to you.
你是个好人  埃里克
you're a good man, eric.
是吗
am i?
这个骨髓
this bone marrow
让他们杀更多无辜的人
lets them kill more innocent people
这样我们的人民才能生存
so that our people can live.
就像马库斯说的
like marcus said...
我们翻开新的一页
"we turn the page.
如月之恒  如日之升
we do better today than we did yesterday."
克拉克
clarke?
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
发生了什么事
ha ha! what happened?
我还以为  你是怎么做到的
i thought...how?
说来话长
it's a long story.
但我很好
but i'm ok.
是火种
it's the flame.
暗黑指挥官
sheidheda.
我正在解决这个问题
i'm working the problem,
但我需要贝卡的笔记本
but i need becca's book.
好的
ok.
这可以等一等  我们没有多少时间
that can wait. we don't have much time.
我需要你跟我来
i need you to come with me.
我们必须攻下护盾
we have to lower the shield.
贝拉米和奥克塔维亚
bellamy and octavia are waiting
还有加百列的孩子们在等着
with the children of gabriel.
克拉克  我不能和你一起去
clarke, i can't go with you.
如果她再醒过来
if she wakes up again,
暗黑指挥官会杀了她的
sheidheda will kill her.
我来利用赖克
ok. i'll use ryker.
反正反应堆就在机器车间下面
the reactor's beneath the machine shop anyway.
不  赖克把厄科送了进来  他不会帮你的
no. ryker turned echo in. he won't help you.
没错
no,
但是约瑟芬很有说服力
but josephine can be very persuasive.
在那之前  答应我你不会
until then, promise me you won't
再取她的骨髓
take any more bone marrow.
现在这不是问题了
that's not a problem now.
这个家族还有另一个夜之血脉
there's another nightblood in the family.
- 妈妈  - 嘘
- mom. - shh.
我不会让他们带走她的
i won't let them take her.
有其母必有其女
like mother, like daughter.
我爱你
i love you.
我也爱你  克拉克
i love you, too, clarke.
现在去救我们所有人
now go save us all...
再一次
again.
赖克
ryker?
如果你帮不了我  也许你妈妈会
if you can't help me, maybe your mom will.
- 把它打开  - 是的  长官
- open it up. - yes, sir.
你在这儿啊
there you are.
杰德说你睡着了
jade said you'd fallen asleep.
我不会错过妈妈的复活
i would never miss mom's resurrection.
不幸的是  厄科还有其他计划
unfortunately, echo had other plans.
这个院子里现在有三个逃跑的杀人犯
there are 3 escaped killers in this compound now.
你们的命令是开枪杀人
your orders are to shoot to kill.
明白了吗
is that clear?
明白
yes, holiness.
他们拿走了他的思维驱动
they took his drive.
我们必须在今晚之前把它拿回来
we have to get it back before tonight
这样我们就能把赖克和其他人一起带回来
so we can bring ryker back with the others.
我来处理吧
i'll handle it.
你的事已经够多了
you've got enough on your plate.
把尸体弄出去
get the body out of here,
把这烂摊子收拾干净
and clean up this mess.
我会让普丽娅帮我的
i'll get priya to help me.
上帝知道她会有动力
lord knows she'll be motivated
去救她的儿子
to save her son.
很好  拿到思维驱动后
good. bring the drive to the lab
把它带到实验室
when you get it.
我要开始其他人的复活
i'll start the other resurrections.
带着守卫
you will take guards.
该死
damn it!
火种又启动了
flame booted me again.
太奇怪了
it's weird.
就像人工智能
it's almost like the ai
在保护暗黑指挥官
is protecting sheidheda.
有人来了
someone's coming.
够了
that's enough.
这是什么
what is this?
他们是宿主
these are the hosts.
你违抗我
you defied me.
我给你拿了骨髓
i got you your doses.
他们是从哪来的
what difference does it make
有什么关系呢
who they came from?
你说得对  没什么关系
you're right. it doesn't.
让这些人离开实验室
get these people out of the lab.
我有事要做
i have work to do.
d区一切正常
sector d is all clear.
你可以带着普莱姆家的人回到圣所
you're free to head back to sanctum with the primes.
我以为我会错过命名
i thought i was gonna miss the namings.
回来后检查h区
check sector h when we get back.
今天我们不能冒险
we can't take any chances today.
命名日吗
naming day?
他们说多个命名  是复数
they said "namings." plural.
加百列
gabriel?
疯狂的自杀者
crazy suiciders.
加百列  你到底在干什么
gabriel, what the hell are you doing?
- 加百列  - 你是说多个命名吗
-gabriel? -you said "namings."
有多少人  谁会回来
how many? who's coming back?
我不知道
i don't know.
我想他们都会
all of them, i think.
我不能让拉塞尔再谋杀无辜的人
i can't have russell murder more innocent people.
我知道这很难  但我们必须
i know it's hard but we have to
按计划行事
stick to the plan!
克拉克攻下护盾
clarke gets the shield down
我们用毒素来分散注意力
and we use the toxin as a distraction
拯救我们的人民
to save our people.
好吧  我有个新计划
yeah, well, i have a new plan:
用注意力干扰策略来阻止命名日
use our distraction to stop naming day.
听着  我很抱歉  但我不像你
look, i'm sorry, but unlike you,
我不能牺牲少数人来拯救大多数人
i can't sacrifice the few to save the many.
怎么这么久
what is taking so long?
应该已经被送到宫殿了
should've been delivered to the palace already.
哦  我的最爱
oh, my favorite.
你确定不想
are you sure you don't want
要个浆果派吗
a jo berry pie?
我讨厌浆果派
i hate jo berry pie.
这是黛利拉的最爱
it was delilah's favorite.
尝尝这些  刚出炉的
try these, fresh out of the oven.
你让黛利拉感到骄傲
you've done delilah proud.
普丽娅  你在这儿啊
priya. there you are.
我到处在找你
i've been looking all over.
约瑟芬  我听说你很有冒险精神
josie. i heard you had quite the adventure.
你不知道  我将告诉你关于这件事的一切
you have no idea, and i'll tell you all about it,
但首先我需要你帮我
but first i need your help with something
在机械车间做点什么
in the machine shop.
赖克现在做了什么
what did ryker do now?
更像是他没做过的事
more like what didn't he do.
爸爸让他把其中一名囚犯干掉
dad asked him to wipe one of the prisoners,
但他完全失去了神经网络
but he's completely lost his nerve.
这很尴尬
it's embarrassing.
他从来都不想面对
he's never wanted to face
我们现在的处境
the reality of our situation.
我们走吧
let's go.
我们不能让他们离开
we can't let them leave.
约瑟芬  来吧
josephine, come on.
我明白了
i knew it.
赖克没有失去神经
ryker didn't lose his nerve,
他失去了生命
he lost his life.
克拉克
clarke.
你看见玛蒂了吗
have you seen madi?
你在这里怎么样
how--how are you here?
听着  我待会再解释
look, i'll explain later.
首先我们要攻下护盾
first we need to lower the shield.
贝拉米在外面
bellamy's out there.
还有骑兵
with the cavalry.
我会让普丽娅帮我
i'll get priya to help me
拆除反应堆
take down the reactor,
然后我们去找玛蒂
and then we go after madi.
卡莱布·梅森
他们像保存奖杯一样保存着宿主的尸骨
they keep the bones of all their hosts like trophies.
他们是穿着皇室长袍的连环杀手
they're serial killers in royal robes
我们在帮助他们
and we're helping them.
我帮助他们为马库斯创建了一个宿主
i helped them create a host for marcus.
这不值得
it wasn't worth it.
你在船上问我的
you asked me that on the ship.
我认为是的  我看不见过去
i thought it was. i couldn't see past
让马库斯回来
getting marcus back.
我看不出你是对的
i couldn't see that you were right.
然后我让克拉克回来了
and then i got clarke back.
我关注我失去了什么
i was focusing on what i lost
而不是我所拥有的
and not what i have.
我不想再那么做了
i don't want to do that anymore.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我为这一切感到抱歉
i'm sorry for all of it.
我偷了药  我让你失望了  真的抱歉
for the drugs. for disappointing you. truly.
很抱歉
i'm sorry for...
我们之间发生的事情
how things have been between us.
我对你的判断不总是公平的
it wasn't always fair how i judged you.
你是人类
you're human.
有时候  身为人类很糟糕
and sometimes, being a human sucks.
我对你做的事情  值得你那样看待我
i deserve to be judged for what i did to you.
我再也不会那样伤害你了
and i will never hurt you that way again.
我可能不算你的母亲
i may not be your mother,
但你是我的家人  瑞文
but you are my family, raven.
请允许我介绍  我们今天
may i present our fourth and fifth
第四次和第五次奇迹
miracles of the day.
欢迎回来  丹尼尔·普莱姆
welcome back daniel prime
凯莉·普莱姆
and kaylee prime.
愿尔名圣
hallowed be their names.
我知道你有多怕
i know how afraid you are.
但背叛朋友并不是答案
but betraying your friends is not the answer.
相信与否  这也对你有利
believe it or not, this is good for you, too.
你俩该去为仪式
i think you two should get changed
准备换装了
for the ceremony.
守卫会带你们去房间的
guards will show you to your suites.
艾比  能帮我点忙吗
abby...can i get your help with something?
等下
wait.
有什么事吗
something wrong?
你只复活了5名普莱姆人
you've only resurrected 5 primes,
但我给了你6颗药剂
but i gave you 6 doses.
我们要的宿主都齐了
we have all the hosts we need.
艾比  抱歉不得不这样做
i'm sorry it has to be this way, abby,
我带走了你的女儿
but i took your daughter.
如你所言  你永远都
as you said, you would never be
放不下这件事了
able to get past that.
我知道我不能
i know i wouldn't.
不  放开她
no, leave her alone!
瑞文  住手
raven, stop!
他们会杀了你的  别去
they'll kill you! don't!
别去
don't do this!
杰克逊
jackson!
不
no!
在日落点
at the sun's set,
请来宫殿和我们一起
please join us on the palace level
见证圣所的奇迹
to bear witness to the miracle of sanctum.
普丽娅
* priya *
永生
* oh, eternal life *
愿她名圣
* hallowed be her name *
欢乐
* oh, rejoice and... *
是他
it's him!
别动
don't move!
- 守卫  立即包围他  - 跪下
- guards, surround him now. - on your knees.
含垢忍辱
eat dirt!
在人群前来参加命名礼之前
get him out of here before the crowd
带他离开这里
arrives for the naming.
带他去见拉塞尔·普莱姆
take him to russell prime.
走吧
let's go.
愿她名圣
* hallowed be thy *
加百列
gabriel.
你好  拉塞尔
hello, russell.
在荒野待了70年
70 years in the wilderness,
而今天你却大摇大摆的来了
and today, you just waltz right in.
你是来杀我的吧
i suppose you're here to kill me.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
双眼皮
○
-
从来都没想这样
it's never been about that.
我是来阻止杀戮的
i'm here to stop the killing.
请取消命名仪式
please. just cancel the namings.
你没必要一直这样
you don't have to keep doing this.
你现在一定明白
surely by now, you can see that
没有死亡  活着就没有意义
without death, life is meaningless.
省省你的哲学道理吧  圣地亚哥医生
save your philosophy lessons, dr. santiago.
你来晚了
you're too late.
复活已经完成
the resurrections are done.
宿主有幸
the hosts were honored
为普莱姆人驱使
to become one with their primes.
大多如此
most of them, anyway.
只因为我们欺骗了他们
only because we lied to them.
都过去了
that's over now.
我来的路上看到了涂鸦
i saw the graffiti on my way in.
只是时间问题而已
it's just a matter of time.
真理的力量无可匹敌
there is nothing more powerful than the truth.
你错了  信仰才是
you're wrong. faith is.
当他们的神一同回归时
when their gods return en masse,
他们也会回来的
they'll get back in line,
那些不回来的人
and those who don't, well,
还可以执行调整协议
there's always the adjustment protocol.
你用更多的凶杀来解决凶杀
your answer to murder is more murder.
年轻的身体说着老成的话
says the old man in the young body.
圣地亚哥医生几世
dr. gabriel santiago the what?
五世还是六世来着
the fifth or sixth of his line?
我不想这样  我已准备好赴死
i didn't want this. i was ready to die.
那就去死吧
so die.
拉塞尔  这具身体  这个人
russell, this body, this man,
是某个人的儿子
he was someone's son,
是某个人的兄弟
someone's brother,
他因我被杀
and he was killed for me.
那些征服了死亡的人
all the man who conquered death wants
只想死去
is to die.
今晚  我让你得偿所愿
tonight, you'll get your wish.
请注意  侦测到赤日毒素
attention. red sun toxin detected.
请前往您的指定区域
make your way to your assigned location.
我来可没打算送死
my itinerary didn't mention that.
请注意
attention...
你回来的这天出现了赤日毒素警报
the red sun alarm on the day you return.
前往您的指定区域等待评估
your assigned location for evacuation.
仍然没有出现日食
and without an eclipse, no less.
你忘了我也会操控
you forget i know how to manipulate
赤日毒素吧
the red sun toxin, too.
太早了  我们必须先攻下护盾
it's too soon. we have to get that shield down.
叫醒她
wake her up.
普丽娅  普丽娅
priya. priya.
我们需要你帮忙
we need your help.
该死  加百列
damn it, gabriel.
我可能阻止不了复活
i may not be able to stop these resurrections,
但我可以保证  毁掉思维驱动
but i can make sure they're the last
他们就是最后一批受害者
by destroying the mind drives,
先从你开始
starting with yours.
会很简单的
we'll make this very simple.
你拆掉反应器  我们就交出赖克
take down the reactor and you get ryker back.
如果你不从
if you don't...
懂了吗
are we clear?
不  等等
no, wait!
如果你想要我的驱动
if you want my drive,
那你们就杀了我
you're going to have to shoot me.
几秒内  守卫
in a few seconds, the guards
就会疏散我们去赖克的地方
are going to evacuate us to ryker's keep.
你也有足够的子弹杀了他们
you have enough bullets to kill them, too.
问题是  你会杀吗
the question is, will you?
长官  我们需要疏散
sir, we need to evacuate.
放下武器
drop it!
立刻出去
get out right now.
别动
don't move.
让他杀了我
let him kill me.
然后开枪  去找我妻子
then open fire and get my wife.
她会知道怎么做
she'll know what to do.
你可没有胆量做神
you never had the stomach to be a god.
抱歉  我的朋友
i am sorry, my friend.
把他绑了
tie him up.
召集剩余的普莱姆
gather the rest of the primes.
关掉警报
turn off that damn alarm!
我的孩子们  冷静
my children, calm yourselves. calm.
没有日食
there is no eclipse.
命名仪式会如期举行
the namings will go on as planned.
你们的神今晚都会回归
all of your gods will return tonight.
我还有更多好消息
and i have more good news.
那个恶魔加百列已经被捕
the demon gabriel has been captured.
今晚  我们要彻底
tonight, we will vanquish his evil
终结他的恶行
once and for all
为圣所的光辉荣耀
and usher in a new era of wonder
迎来奇迹的新纪元
for the glory and grace of sanctum.
为圣所的光辉荣耀
丹尼尔  凯莉  见见你们的新朋友
daniel, kaylee, meet your new old friends.
这位是迦勒和贾丝明  这位是米兰达
this is caleb and jasmine, and this is miranda.
他们是兄弟姐妹
they're brother and sister.
你知道是吧
you know that, right?
告诉我
tell me.
你们背叛朋友时
did you even hesitate
犹豫过吗
to betray your friends?
不理他
ignore him.
一两个世纪后
in a century or two,
你不会记着这些小事的
you won't even remember these petty concerns.
也不会忘
and to forget,
你们要做的  就是放弃你们的灵魂
all you have to do is give up your soul.
护盾
the shield.
早就说她会这么做的
told you she'd do it.
普莱姆去死
death to primes!
去死
death!
你怎么才过来
what took you so long?
我不想打断你们的相聚
i hate to cut the moment short,
但是拉塞尔告诉人们那是一个
but russell told the people that it was
假的警报
a false alarm.
他们没有启动疏散机制
they're not evacuating.
我们没有干扰成功
we have no distraction.
我们剩下的朋友还陷入麻烦之中
the rest of our friends are still in trouble,
并且我们也没有足够的人手
and we don't have the people
一起战斗
to fight our way through.
我们不是来战斗的
we're not here to fight.
我们是来解放他们的
we're here to liberate.
贝拉米说得对
bellamy's right,
而我们唯一需要的武器就是真相
and the only weapon we need for that is truth.
你这语气听起来像加百列
you sound like gabriel.
加百列人呢
where is gabriel?
他为什么这么快就拉响了警报
and why did he set off the alarm so soon?
如果我们只是把事实真相告诉他们  他们是不会相信的
they won't believe us just because we tell them the truth.
你有什么想法
what are you thinking?
我的想法是赖克帮我们挑起了这件事
i'm thinking ryker helped us start this.
应该让他妈妈来结束它
his mother will finish it.
他们觉得我是约瑟芬
they think i'm josephine,
所以我不能拿着
so it can't be me.
远处楼梯上有动静
we've got movement up the far stairs.
普丽娅·普莱姆  不要开枪
priya prime! don't shoot!
电力已经停了  护盾也被破坏了
the power is out, the shield is down,
但我们不是来和你们战斗的
but we are not here to fight.
我有些话想对你们说
i have something to tell you
忠言逆耳
that will be hard to hear,
但都是事实
but it's the truth.
普莱姆家族说我们是你们的敌人
the primes told you that we're your enemy.
他们骗了你们
they lied.
所有事情都是在骗你们
they lied about everything.
他们并不是神
they're not gods.
他们不会和宿主们融为一体
they don't become one with their hosts.
他们只会杀了宿主
they kill them.
他们偷走你们的身体
they steal your bodies
这样他们就能长命百岁
so they can live forever.
告诉他们
tell them.
这是真的
it's true.
我们不是神
we're not divine.
打开它
open it.
我们之所以活下来是因为我们拥有技术
we survive because we have technology.
但我们需要你们的身体才能成功
but we need your bodies to do it.
黛利拉并没有与我共生
delilah's not one with me.
她死了
she's dead,
杀了她之后我才能复活
killed so that i could return.
全部都是一个谎言
it's all a lie.
全是谎言
all lies.
骗子
liars!
我对你很失望  普丽娅
i am disappointed in you, priya.
我对你们所有人都很失望
i'm disappointed in all of you.
根据我们的调整协议
according to our adjustment protocol...
非信徒必须被净化掉
nonbelievers must be purified!
我感觉到了
aah! i feel it!
我们全都死定了
eee! we're all gonna die!
所有人  赶紧拿出抗毒素
everybody, antitoxin, now.
深呼吸  你们能撑两个小时
breathe deeply. you're good for two hours.
打开调节器的处理房间
unlock the processing room for the adjusters.
让他们把毒素全用了
tell them to use it all.
把犯人从实验室带到圣厅里
move the prisoners from the lab to the great hall.
非信徒们
disbelievers!
普丽娅去哪儿了
where the hell is priya?
毒素把我们分开了
the toxin separated us.
人群挡在我们中间
the crowd got between us.
去死吧  非信徒们
die, nonbeliever! uhh!
救救他们  为了黛利拉  求你们了
help them, please, for delilah.
杀人犯
murderer!
全都给我回来
all of you, get back!
我会把你们全都杀了的
i will kill you all!
不
no.
贾克斯
jax?
jax!
你不能过去
you can't.
别对我施命令
i do not take orders from you anymore!
米勒  她说得没错
miller, she's right.
你打不过那些守卫的
you'll never make it past the guards.
没错  但我可以
no, but i can.
我和你一起去
i'm going with you.
- 盖亚  - 他们只会觉得我是约瑟芬的守卫
- gaia. - they'll think i'm josephine's guard.
是玛蒂在叫  我要过去
it's madi. i'm going.
好的
ok.
米勒  你留在这里
miller, stay here
保护剩下的人
and protect the others.
我会把他带回来的  相信我
i'll get him back. trust me.
渎神者
blasphemers. .
伙计们
uh, guys?
我们有麻烦了
we've got a problem.
把入侵者们杀掉
kill the invaders! aah!
- 快走  - 你要做什么
- go. - what will you do?
听着  我还没有想好  但你快走
look, i'm still working on that part. just go!
米勒  放下武器  我们并不想杀他们  好吗
miller, weapons down. we don't want to kill them, ok?
但他们想杀我们
they want to kill us.
快走
move in!
如果我们开始反抗  这将变成一场大屠杀
if we start fighting, it will turn into a bloodbath.
我们得找个地方躲起来  耐心等着
we need to take cover and wait it out.
跟我过来
follow me!
谢天谢地
thank god.
你去哪儿了
where have you been?
我在找普丽娅
i was looking for priya.
但我后来被加百列的疯孩子们
but then i was blocked by a bunch of
挡住了去路
gabriel's lunatic children.
对了  普丽娅死了
she's dead, by the way.
这到底是怎么回事
what the hell is going on?
我们要离开圣所  直到这里净化完毕
we're leaving sanctum until it's purified.
妈妈
mom.
你妈妈杀死了她妈妈
your mother murdered her mother.
很讽刺  不是吗
ironic, don't you think?
你他妈别对我说话
don't you speak to me. uhh!
我怎么会爱过一个叛徒
how could i have ever loved such a traitor?
亲爱的
oh, sweetheart.
至少你结束了那段感情
at least you have closure.
够了
that's enough.
既然人都到齐了
now that we're all accounted for,
我们这就出发吧
it's time to go.
你们都服用抗毒素了吗
have you all taken the antitoxin?
出发  去哪儿
go? where?
当然是去太空了
to space, of course.
圣所已经失去了我们
sanctum has lost us.
至少目前是
for now, anyway.
我们没有飞行员  普丽娅死了
we have no pilot. priya's dead.
没准儿都是因为你杀死了李家人
maybe if you didn't kill the lees.
这不成问题
that won't be a problem.
我们不需要李家人来开
we don't need the lees,
是不是  瑞文
do we, raven?
你自己去开吧  杀人犯
go float yourself, murderer.
你现在同意了吗
how about now?
我给你3秒钟时间
you have 3 seconds.
1...2...
好的
ok.
明智的选择
good choice.
太棒了
excellent.
守卫们  带上罪犯
guards, take the prisoners.
- 是  先生  - 我们从隧道离开
- yes, sir. - we're using the tunnel,
但要时刻保持警惕
but be prepared for anything.
再见了  老朋友  圣所是你的了
good-bye, old friend. sanctum is yours,
但我怀疑你撑不了多久了
though i suspect you won't last very long.
你们不一起走吗
you're not coming?
你杀了她
you killed her.
她只是想帮你  但你杀了她
all she did was help and you killed her.
我们要留下
we're staying.
我们要救我们的人
we're gonna save our people.
我为你感到自豪  墨菲
i'm proud of you, murphy.
你知道吗
just so you know,
约瑟芬会叫我  约翰
josephine called me "john."
约瑟芬  丹尼尔  凯莉  有什么问题吗
josie, daniel, kaylee, is there a problem?
他们改变了注意  俩懦夫
they changed their minds. cowards.
浪费思维驱动实在是太可惜了
the mind drive is a terrible thing to waste.
约瑟芬  带上你的守卫  咱们走吧
josie, bring your guards and let's go.
守卫  走吧
guards, move out.
等等
wait.
她在里面
she's one of them.
把她扔进狼群
throw her to the wolves.
不
no.
我在克拉克的思维里看到她了
i saw her in clarke's mind.
把那个孩子作为要挟  也许对瑞文管用
threatening the child may work on raven,
但如果我说得没错的话  我们需要她
but if i'm right, we need her
一起上飞船
to get on that ship.
运输船舶一切正常
transport ship is secure.
开启气闸  气闸正常
airlock engaged. airlock secure.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177